http://www.hinz.org.nz/?page=privacy

Privacy Policy - Health Informatics New Zealand
Search »
JOIN HINZ   |   Print Page   |   Contact Us   |   Report Abuse   |   Sign In
HomeNEWS
SIGN UP for eNewslettersSIGN UP for Nursing eNewsView eNews ArchiveeHN Home PageBrowse all NewsAbout eHealthNewseHN ChannelseHN TeameHN EditorialeHN AdvertisingeHN Ad SpecseHN Publishing DatesFAQ eHealthNews.nz
WATCH
Webinar SeriesAbout eHealthTVeHTV Webcast AccesseHTV Webcast ScheduleeHTV Webcast LibraryeHTV Studio at ConferenceeHTV Studio BookingseHTV Pop Up Studio ServiceSample WebcastWebcast FAQLogin FAQ
EVENTS
2021 Digital Health Week NZ
Why Attend DHWNZExhibit at DHWNZ
Why ExhibitHow to book a boothExhibitors HiNZ 2021
2020 Networking Events2021 Leadership Summit
Attend SummitSponsor SummitFAQ Summit
2020 DHWNZ CancelledWebinar Series 2020
Future Webinars
Telehealth-building a lasting service post-crisisTechnology to support organisational resilienceBusiness Intelligence driving healthcare transform
Past Webinars
Digital Transformation in the era of Covid-19UK Digital TransformationDigital Transformation in the era of Covid-19 – 2Technology Solutions to help fight a pandemicDigital Hospitals: stories from South Island DHBsSpark Health Digital Innovation ProgrammeAI driving clinical decision makingDigitising patient reported outcomesAged care goes digitalUK’s Virtual Summer School – NZ SessionHealthcare cloud transformationDigital labs and the response to Covid-19eMental Health and the pandemicCovid-19 contact tracing - national solutionsEMR – a strategic sustainable approach
Event CalendarWebcast LibraryHiNZ PrimersFAQ COVID-19
SPONSOR
AdvertisePress releaseSponsor WebinarsSponsor SummitSponsor DHWNZPop Up StudioPromote Your Company
JOIN
Member LoginCOMMUNITY
About CiLNCiLN Award InfoCiLN Member TipsCiLN FAQNurse Special Interest GroupCHIA-NZ Working GroupStudent Membership
Why join HiNZ?Join HiNZJoin CiLNJoin Health Forum NZOrder member badgeWebcastFAQ for members
LEARN
Webcast LibraryEarn CPD PointsUniversity CoursesOnline Courses
RESOURCES
Member LoginHIMSS AccessJob SeekersJob AdvertisementsEducation OptionsCOVID-19 ResourcesTools for Busy PeopleHiNZ Acronym DictionaryHiNZ Cartoon GalleryHiNZ Conference ArchiveHiNZ Event ArchiveHiNZ eNewsletterHealth Informatics ResourcesAffiliate organisationsMessaging CentreUseful Links
ABOUT
What is Health Informatics?
Government Digital Health
About HiNZHiNZ Board Members
Board RoleHow to voteBoard Candidates 2021
HiNZ Management TeamPrivacy PolicySocial MediaContact Us
Edit This Favorite
Name:
Category:
Share:
Yes
No, Keep Private
Privacy Policy
Share
|
Privacy Act
Health Informatics New Zealand (HiNZ) is committed to protecting your privacy. Your personal data is protected in New Zealand by the Privacy Act. This provides, amongst other things, that the data we hold about you should be processed lawfully and fairly. It should be accurate, relevant and not excessive. The information should be kept up to date, where necessary, and not retained for longer than is necessary. You have the right to see what is held about you and correct any inaccuracies. HiNZ treats all the data held with the utmost care and security. Any details you give will remain confidential. If you have questions about your data please contact us anytime.
Member data
If you are an individual member of HiNZ you will be provided with a Username and Password for the HiNZ website. The default setting for Member Profile visibility is set to 'Members only'. Members also have the option to 'toggle' these settings to 'on/off' under their Member Profile once they are signed in to the site. Visitors to the site who perform a site search will see the member's name but will not have access to the member's profile. If you are a member and your email address is set to 'Private' (not visible in profile) it will not be displayed to other members, but members can still contact you via email through the site's group email system.
eNewsletter data
All HiNZ members, HiNZ event delegates and eNewsletter subscribers automatically receive our fortnightly email newsletter. We may contact our eNewsletter database from time to time with promotional offers from HiNZ or HiNZ sponsors. If you decide you no longer wish to receive the eNewsletter please follow the unsubscribe instructions contained within the email.
Event registration data
When you attend a HiNZ event, your name, job title and organisation name may be included in our published delegates list, but your email address and other contact details always remain private. These are not visible to exhibitors and sponsors. Our conference app enables delegates to message each other securely and privately without disclosing your email address (unless you opt in to provide it).
Questions?
If you have questions about our privacy policy or your personal data please contact us anytime.
Sign In
Login with Facebook
Login with LinkedIn
OR
Remember Me
Forgot your password?Haven't joined yet?
eHealthNews
more
4 hours agoBay of Plenty going live with interactive regional portal
5/10/2020Telehealth national standards in pipeline
Event Calendar
more
14/10/2020Webinar: Telehealth - building a lasting service post-crisis23/10/2020Webinar: Technology to support organisational resilience – CDHB case study
HiNZ, PO Box 300125, Albany, Auckland 0752, New Zealand.
Membership Management Software Powered by YourMembership  ::  Legal
